https://www.adagio.com/pages/privacy_policy.html

Order
To complete an order, our visitors must share with us contact information
(name, e-mail and shipping address) and billing information (credit card
number and expiration date).
This information is used to create an account
to process and ship your orders.
Newsletter
We invite visitors to subscribe to our TeaMuse newsletter, and ask for
e-mail contact information to assist in its distribution.
All customers
receive updates of new TeaMuse issues automatically.
Should you wish to
not receive these, you may easily opt-out.
Please see Choice/Opt-Out
section for more info.
Tea-of-the-Month Club
We offer a number of tea-of-the-month clubs.
Each allows our customers to
receive teas automatically over a period of time.
These are processed as
any other order, with the exception that the delivery is not immediate, but
is spread over many months.
Again, all information gathered is for the sole
purpose of fulfilling an order, and is not used for any other purpose or
shared with any third parties.
Surveys
From time-to-time our site requests information from users by way of
surveys.
For example, our 'e-mail us' form has survey information.
Participation in these surveys is always voluntary and the visitor therefore
has a choice whether or not to disclose this information.
Information
requested occasionally includes contact information (such as name and
shipping address), tea preferences and demographic information (such as zip
code, age level).
Survey information will be used for purposes of
monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site.
This
information is used for aggregate analysis, and is not ties to any
individual visitor or combined with any other information we may gather.
Furthermore, the survey conducted by BizRate at the conclusion of a purchase
is solely under the discretion of BizRate, and is governed by this company's
own privacy statement.
Tea Reviews
We invite our customers to submit reviews of the products they have
purchased earlier.
This information is then displayed on our site to aid
other visitors' shopping experience.
These submissions are always
voluntary, and the only personal information requested is customer's name.
To reward customers for taking the time to complete these, for each review
submitted we deduct $0.50 off a subsequent order.
Tell-A-Friend
We invite our customers to mail friends an introductory free $5
gift-certificate.
This is meant to encourage a visit to our store.
To
facilitate this, we ask for the name and e-mail address of the recipient.
This information is used to electronically mail a unique certificate code,
keep track and assure an accurate credit of five dollars at the time of the
purchase.
This information is not traded or shared with any third parties.
Live Help
To make shopping with us more enjoyable, we offer the benefits of a 'live
help' feature.
This allows a visitor to chat in real time with our customer
representatives.
The only information requested during a 'live chat'
session is a visitor's first name.
This information is used to visually
differentiate the comments made by both parties, and is not stored, nor used
in conjunction with any other personal information gathered by this site.
The software that make 'live help' possible is the property of Live Person,
Inc.
Please be aware that Adagio Teas is not responsible for the privacy
practices of this company.
Special Offers
Our customers will occasionally receive information on products, services,
special deals, and a newsletter. Out of respect for the privacy of our
customers we present the option to not receive these types of
communications. Please see the Choice/Opt-out section below.
On rare occasions it may be necessary to send out a strictly service-related
announcement.
For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for
maintenance we might send you an email.
Generally, users may not opt-out of
these communications.
However, these communications are not promotional in
nature, and are extremely infrequent.
Cookies
A cookie is a piece of personal account data stored on the customer's hard
drive containing info that will enhance the enjoyment of our site.
For
example, a cookie containing a record of past orders provides such useful
features as an opportunity to easily reorder or refill any of our teas, and
post reviews of the items previously purchased, as well as receive
recommendation of the items we feel you will particularly enjoy.
You may control whether your computer will accept cookies (from Adagio Teas,
BizRate or LivePerson) with the preference setting of your browser.
If
your browser is set to reject cookies, you may still visit and shop at our
site.
The only drawback is that some of the experience-enhancing features
listed above will not be active.
Log Files
Logs are the information created and stored by the server and include such
data as a visitor's IP (internet protocol) address, browser type, ISP
(internet service provider), referring/exit pages, platform type, and
date/time stamp.
This information is used to analyze macro traffic trends,
administer the site, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate
use.
None of the information collected in this matter may be used to
ascertain the personal identity of any of our visitors.
With whom this information is shared
Adagio Teas is the sole owner of the information collected on this site.
We do not sell or rent this information to any third party. The only companies
with whom some information is shared are USPS, UPS, Fedex, DHL, Asendia and PayPal.
We use USPS, Fedex and UPS to ship orders, and PayPal gateway to bill users
for goods and services. These companies do not retain, share, store or use
personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes.
We may also share this information with third party service providers to
serve online personalized messages and offers on our behalf. You can always
opt out of these by unchecking the "email marketing" box in your account page.
Card-linked offers
By registering a payment card (e.g., debit card or credit card) in connection with transaction monitoring, you authorize Adagio Teas to share your payment card information with the applicable payment network(s) (such as MasterCard, VISA, and American Express) so they know you enrolled, in addition to Linkable Networks, which acts as our service provider in making available offers linked to your payment card. You authorize the applicable payment network(s) and Linkable Networks to monitor transactions on your registered card(s) to identify qualifying purchases in order to determine whether you have qualified for or earned an offer linked to your payment card, and for MasterCard, VISA, and American Express to share such transaction details with Linkable Networks and Adagio to enable my offer(s).
For additional information regarding Linkable Networks' privacy practices, please see Linkable Networks Privacy Policy. You may opt-out of transaction monitoring on specific card(s) you have registered by visiting your account page.
How you may affect the collection, use and distribution of your information
Correction/Updating Personal Information:
If your personal information changes or if you no longer desire our service,
we provide an easy way to correct, update or remove your personal data.
This may be accomplished with a visit to account page.
We will
happily assist you in this task.
Simply drop us a note at
info@adagio.com.
Choice/Opt-out
We respect your privacy and give you an opportunity to opt-out of receiving
our periodic announcements of sales, promotions and newsletter publication,
as well as email marketing. This may be accomplished with a visit to your account page. We will
happily assist you in this task.
Simply drop us a note at
info@adagio.com.
What security procedures are in place to protect the loss, misuse or
alteration of your personal information.
Adagio Teas takes every precaution to protect our customers' and visitors'
information.
When customers submit sensitive information via our site, your
information is protected both on- and off-line.
All sensitive information (such as credit card numbers) submitted on our
site is encrypted and is protected with the best encryption software in the
industry - SSL.
You may visually verify that the site is secure by looking
for the closed lock icon at the bottom of either a Netscape or Microsoft
browsers.
While we use SSL encryption to protect sensitive information online, we also
do everything in our power to protect user-information off-line.
All of our
visitors' information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above,
is restricted in our offices.
Only employees who need the information to
perform a specific job are granted access to personally identifiable
information.
And these employees are kept up-to-date on our security and
privacy practices.
Finally, the servers that we store personally
identifiable information on are kept in a secure environment, behind a
locked cage.
If you have any questions about the security at our site, please send an
email to info@adagio.com.
We will be happy to answer your questions.
Notification of Changes
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will promptly post those
changes on this page.
We want our visitors to be aware of what information
we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose
it.
If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in
a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will
notify users by way of an email.
Users will have a choice as to whether or
not we use their information in this different manner.
However, if you have
deleted or deactivated your account information, you will not be contacted,
nor will your information be used in this new manner.
We will use
information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the
information was collected.
Recipe: Candy Cane T...
.
$5
OFF
Savings
Coupon!
Email
claim now >>
Applies to any product, but not shipping
.
I have been looking for teas that came close to Teevana teas for a few years and couldn't find anything that I
liked. Well with Asiago t...
Ask us a question.
Anytime!
Questions?
Adagio Chatbot
You may ask me "Where is my order?" or "How much is shipping?" and I will gladly answer your question.
If you don't like my answer, our customer support team will email you a reply shortly. Ask me!
Question
>
.
